{
    "subject": "resource/Dave_Davies",
    "predicate": "ontology/instrument",
    "object": "resource/Harmonica",
    "human_readable": "Dave Davies plays the Harmonica.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7835837006568909,
            "question": "What instrument does Dave Davies play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6928710341453552,
            "question": "Is Dave Davies known for playing any other instruments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6871291995048523,
            "question": "What kind of music might Dave Davies play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6771054863929749,
            "question": "How is the harmonica played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5978875756263733,
            "question": "Is Dave Davies a musician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5507442951202393,
            "question": "Can you name some famous musicians who play the harmonica?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3757212460041046,
            "question": "Are there any famous bands that feature a harmonica player?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36307039856910706,
            "question": "What genre of music might Dave Davies be associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28247854113578796,
            "question": "What is the sound of a harmonica like?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27978768944740295,
            "question": "Are there any popular songs that feature the harmonica?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dave Davies plays the Harmonica.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8378_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the sound of a harmonica like?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8378_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music might Dave Davies be associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8378_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous bands that feature a harmonica player?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8378_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8378_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text focuses on Dave Davies's work as a guitarist and vocalist for The Kinks and his solo career. There is no mention of him playing the harmonica. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not mention anything about Dave Davies playing the harmonica. It discusses his work as a guitarist and songwriter, but there is no information regarding him playing the harmonica."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information in the context provided that suggests Dave Davies plays the harmonica.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Dave Davies playing the harmonica in any of the provided context information.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Dave Davies playing the Harmonica anywhere in the provided context information.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention Dave Davies playing the Harmonica; instead, it focuses on his guitar skills and other musical abilities.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}